蓝光电影网
blu-raydisc.tv
谍影重重5
杰森·伯恩
察曼塔斯 希腊
希腊-阿拉巴尼亚边境村庄
瓦希里 你先上
10块押塞尔维亚人
我押20
押10块赌俄国人
冰岛 雷克雅维克
用数据库攻击他们的资料库
杜布纳 48K
维吉尼亚 兰利
中情局
媒体：对中情局失去信心
下载"黑色行动"文件夹至随身碟中.
警告：侦测到外部追踪
你还能上网
维吉尼亚 麦克林
深梦集团 加利福尼亚
加州 矽谷
意大利 罗马
希腊 雅典
1小时后宪法广场KIOSK咖啡馆见
铁腕   行动
绊脚 石行动
绊脚 石行动\涉及理察·韦伯
涉及理查·韦伯
杰森 伯恩处于监视中
德国 柏林
柏林中央车站
绊脚石行动
美国应对
巨大威胁
议案
理查·韦伯
远程控制 接入已确认 连接完成
行动组已抵达
你还有两分钟.
联合王国（英国） 伦敦
内华达州 拉斯维加斯
局长要见你
左口袋有追踪器 给杜威
情况有些不对
运行预测算法
叙利亚阿勒颇
ALEPPO SYRIA
黑色行动
复制到U盘
下载“黑色行动”至文件夹:U盘
绊脚石计划
中情局主服务器
系统漏洞
理查·韦伯
配偶:玛丽·韦伯
儿子:大卫·韦伯
绊脚石计划
大卫·韦伯
数据库
标记:已知的设备  杜布纳 48k
查看最近的活动
匹配
尼基·帕森斯 绊脚石计划
和杰森·伯恩有关
加密
科维兹广场 49 28764 柏林
阿尔伯特·赫希博士
首席医疗官
绊脚石行动
项目行为分析
杰森·伯恩行为评估
绊脚石行动的所有特工会被训练成为顶尖的刺客
杰森·伯恩招募记录
中央情报局新闻稿
新网络部门负责人希瑟·李
我选择中情局
是因为我觉得我在那里会有所作为
希瑟·李
埃塞特[1号特工]
搜索克里斯托弗·迈克尔
找到一个
实时位置跟踪定位
隐蔽相机
下水道系统
拉斯维加斯公共工程部门
追踪
顾问:
迷失_特工
导演
保罗·格林格拉斯
我记得
I remember.
这一切我都记得
I remember everything.
韦伯上校 早安
Captain Webb. Good morning
我说的这些你都听懂了吗
Has everything been explalined to you?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
当这一切结束之时 你就不再是大卫·韦伯了
When we are finished with you, you will no longer be David Webb.
长官 我会成为您需要我成为的人
I'll be whoever you need me to be, sir.
如果你选择继续参与这项计划
You knew exaclty what it meant for you
你应当知道这对你来说意味着什么
if you chose to stay.
杰森 你不能逃避你以前做过的一切
You can't outrun what you did, Jason.
是你造就了今天的你 你清楚知道自己是谁
You made yourself and know who you are.
最终你将不得不面对这样一个事实
Eventually you're gonna have to face the fact.
你是自愿加入这个计划的
You volunteered.
不 我的上帝
Oh no. My god!
克里斯蒂安·达索预订了
Christian Dassault made a reservation.
快点 进来
Come on, get in.
希瑟·李
Heather Lee.
女士 我们追踪到一台电脑
Ma'am we have a device.
它曾于 1993年被派发给驻扎
Issued to a stay behind team in Novosibirsk, Rassia in 1993.
在我们的设备清单中它被标注为“已摧毁”
Marked on our inventory as destroyed.
有人在用它访问我们的服务器
It's knocking on our front door.
现在情况如何
What's the status?
无论是谁在操作那台电脑 它目前毫无动静
Whoever it is, is just sitting there, idle.
让开
Move!
他们发现了一个后门
They found a back-door.
给我一段反向追踪代码 我要定位设备使用人的位置
We need the reverse shell. I'm going to locate the source.
我正在努力
I'm working on it.
大家都听着 我们装有机密文件的主服务器被人攻破了
Okay, people, we have a major breach in our classified main-frame.
所有人马上放下手中的工作 把这个漏洞补上
Drop everything you're doing and get on it, right now.
女士 我已经把代码发给你了
Ma'am, I'm sending you the shell.
收到了
Got it.
找到个IP
Got an IP.
雷克雅维克(冰岛首都)
Reykjavik.
萨科夫的骇客基地  切断那栋建筑的供电
- Sakov's hacking camp. - Kill the power to the building.
马上黑进他们的供电网 是 长官
- Get into that power grid, now. - Yes, sir.
我已经搞到那栋建筑的供电开关了  听我指挥
- I've got the power to the building. - Standby.
10秒 我们现在有视频
- 10 seconds. - We got vid now.
已经投影到达屏幕
Get on top of it.
访问网格
Accessing the grid.
切断电源 收到 正在切断电源
- Shut it down. - Copy that. Shutting it down.
我是杜威（中情局局长罗柏·杜威）
Dewey.
我们刚刚被黑了
We've just been hacked.
现在情况有多糟
How badly?
可能比史诺登泄密事件还严重些
Could be worse than Snowden.
现在有什么线索吗 我们还在查
- Is there any attribution? - We're working on it.
网络安全部门说骇客肯定对我们的系统十分了解
Lee says it must be someone with a deep knowledge of our systems.
这可能影响到深梦计划和铁腕计划的实施
This could affect Deep Dream and Iron Hand.
我要一份这次安全事故的汇报
I want a briefing.
一小时之内送到简报室来
In my conference room in one hour.
确认了吗 是的 刚刚他们被黑了
- Did you get confirmation? - Yeah, there was a hack.
所以我们暴露了吗
So are we exposed?
还不清楚 我们正在调查
We don't know yet. We're checking.
现在联系杜威 今天晚上安排一次会议
I want you to call Dewey, set up a meeting this evening.
亚伦,我们还有很多股份在这
Aaron, we have a lot at stake here.
或许我们应该开始调查 就这样做
Maybe we should run a probe. Just do it.
乔治 发布会准备的怎么样了
Hey, George, are we ready for the launch?
海伦 这位是国家情报总管
Heather, you know the Director of National Intelligence.
我是希瑟 李 网络安全部 长官
Heather Lee, Cyber Ops, sir.
查到了是谁干的么
Have you got a name for us?
这位黑客是一位前中情局特工
Our hacker was a former Agency operative.
情报表明她目前在克里斯蒂安 德赛特手下工作
Believed to be working with Christian Dassault,  and ...
并且她与杰森·伯恩之间有所联系
previously linked to Jason Bourne.
伯恩
Bourne?
老天爷
Jesus Christ.
他们拿到了什么资料
What did they get?
黑色行动的文件 包括从"踏脚石行动"到"铁腕计划"的所有资料
Black ops files, from TreadStone, all the way to Iron Hand.
"铁腕计划"也泄露了
Iron Hand?
这计划甚至还没开始实施呢
That's not even operational yet, for Christ's sakes.
这个妮基·帕尔森现在在哪
Where is Nicky Parsons right now?
她目前在行动中
On the move.
她从雷克雅未克出发 取道布加勒斯特(罗马尼亚首都)到达雅典
She left Reykjavik traveling through Bucharest to Athens.
感觉她准备要和谁碰面
Feels like a meet to me.
这事你打算怎么处理
How are you going to handle it?
我们要从源头解决问题
We cut the head off this thing.
长官 我请求参与这次行动
Sir, I'd like to be point on this operation.
你甚至还没有阅读那些秘密文件的权限
You're not indoctrinated for this material.
实际上我已经参与到这次行动中了
I'm already into it.
,我在帕森斯下载的文件里注入了一段追踪代码
I embedded malware into Parsons' download.
如果有人打开那些文件 我能定位到他们的位置
When those files are opened, I can trace them.
让我加入这次行动吧
Let me in.
我会找到帕森斯和那些文件的位置
I'll deliver Parsons, the files,
如果伯恩和帕森斯在一起 我还能帮你找到伯恩
And if he's out there, I'll give you Bourne, too.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
我很欣赏你的工作热情
I appreciate you enthusiasm.
但是
But...
不要再把你的个人意愿强加给国家情报主管
Do not push your personal agenda to the DNI again.
明白
Understood.
好吧 我相信你能在这次行动中大展身手
Alright, I think you can help me.
我会把这次行动的最高指挥权交给你
I'm going to give you full operational control on this.
你有权限调动任何相关人员和资源去完成这次行动
And I'll assure that you have access to any relevant teams and resources.
同时我需要知道你所做的每一步决策
And I want to know every move you make.
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
非常感谢您
Thank you very much, sir.
什么事
Yeah.
我现在需要你帮忙
I need your help now.
我这边的事还没搞定
I'm not finished here.
杰森·伯恩现身了
Jason Bourne is in play.
他在哪
Where?
雅典 罗马的事先解决
Athens, close your accout in Rome.
明白
Understood.
不要 不要 不要
No. No. No.
不要 不要
No, no.
我们刚从监控设备发现 帕森斯半小时前登上了一辆公车
We got a hit from a CCTV feed. Parsons boarded a bus half-hour ago
向雅典城西边去了 我们那边有两只小队待命
headed west across Athens. I got two local teams en route.
发现了伯恩的踪迹吗 目前还没有
- Any sign of Bourne? - Not so far.
我有预感 他肯定在这起骇客事件中参了一脚
He's involved in this somehow, I can feel it.
把所有在雅典的监控设备投到荧幕上
Upload all Athens data on feeds.
启动实时监测处理系统
Activate real time processing.
明白
Copy that.
我们的特工就位了吗
Where are we?
卡尔森手下的特工刚刚抵达宪法广场
Carson's bus has just arrived at Syntayma Square.
希腊国会大厦前有不少示威人群
There's a demonstration in front of the Greek parliament building.
我认为她想利用人群作为掩护
I think she'll use it as cover.
把A小组和B队部署到广场周围
Deploy Alpha and Bravo to the square.
我们要在国会大厦外的人群中找到帕森斯
Recon for Parsons in the crowd outside the Parliament,
还要排查附近她所有可能与伯恩会面的地方
and any possible rendezvous points.
明白 长官
Copy that, sir.
长官 明白 一号特工刚抵达雅典
Sir, the asset has landed.
A小组已经抵达广场
Alpha Team arriving now.
收到
Copy that.
刚收到A小组传来的视讯信号
I have the Alpha Team feed.
投到荧幕上
Pull them up.
雅典警方已经开始派遣战术分队驱散示威者了
Athens police are reporting tactical teams moving on the demonstrators.
切断广场附近电子设备与社交软件服务器之间的网络连接
Isolate all social media posts from the Square.
好的 长官
Yes, ma'am.
重放一下A小组1号监视设备情况
Rewind Alpha 1's feed.
好的 长官 倒回20秒
Yes, ma'am. 20 seconds.
什么事
What's wrong?
我帮克里斯蒂安·达索
I hacked into the Agency.
黑进了中情局的服务器
For Christian Dassault.
我拿到了所有黑色行动的资料 我们准备将它们公之于众
I got all the black ops files, we're putting them online.
我们得走了
We need to move.
停
Stop.
倒回2秒 有个长发女人
2 seconds forward. Blonde hair.
放大
Enhance.
找到她
Find her.
我跟你说 跟达索走的太近  会害死你自己的
I told you, Christian Dassault is going to get you killed.
杰森 我们已经无路可
We don't have a choice, Jason.
他们现在发起了一项新的计划
It's started again. A new program.
代号“铁腕计划“ 相比之前之前更糟糕
Iron Hand. It's even worse than before.
那跟我有什么关系
What's that got to do with me?
事很重要 当然跟你有关系
Because it matters. It matters.
我觉得那不关我的事
Not too me, it doesn't.
现在最重要的事是活下去
All that matters is staying alive.
远离电子设备 你就能幸存下来
You get off the grid. Survive.
我可不认同你这个说
I don't believe that, and neither do you.
看看你自己
Look at yourself.
看看你现在活成什么样子
Look at what you're doing.
你不能再这么活下去
You can't live like this for much longer.
杰森 我来找你是因为我发现了一些事情
Jason, I came here because I found something.
我在“绊脚石计划”的记录文件中看到了你父亲的名字
I found your father's name in the Treadstone files.
他只不过是一个数据分析师 肯定不会参与那些行动
He was an analyst. He wasn't in operations.
他跟那些肮脏的计划毫无关联
He wasn't near any of that stuff.
我跟你所说的这些 都是我亲眼所见
I'm telling you what I saw.
似乎你的父亲与那项计划有着直接联系
It looked like he was involved directly.
文件里还有很多有关你本人的资料
And there's more. More about you.
你看到了些什么
What do you mean?
在你加入到那个项目之前他们就在监视你了
Before you joined the program, they were watching you.
监视我
Watching me?
杰森 为了了解事情的真相
You've tortured yourself for a long time now, Jason.
一直以来你都饱受煎熬
You tortured yourself for what you've done.
但是你对他们对你所做的一切仍然一无所知
But you don't know the truth about what they did to you.
你需要知道那些文件
You need to read those files.
快走 他们盯上你了
Move. They tracked you.
A小组一号发现一位男性目标 一位女性目标
Alpha 1 has eyes on two targets. One female, one male.
确认男性目标的身份 明白 长官
- Identify the male. - Copy that, sir.
A小组1号 请确认男性目标的身份
Alpha 1. We need an ID on the male target.
在警方包围这片区域之前我们得离开这里
You gotta get out of here before the police cut off this part of the city.
往北走
Head north.
我们在雅典娜雕像那里会合
Meet me at the Statue of Athena.
我去把他们引开
I'll take them with me.
那就是杰森·伯恩
That's him.
现在行动
Now.
盯紧伯恩
Stay with Bourne.
允许消灭目标
Clear to engage the target.
收到
Copy.
A小组 盯紧伯恩 你可以干掉目标
Alpha team, stay with the male. You are clear to engage.
跟上
Come on.
长官 A小组通讯中断
Sir, Alpha Team comms are down.
丢失目标 长官 伯恩把他们杀了
We've lost him, sir. He's taken them out.
找到帕森斯 他肯定会回来找她的
Find Parsons! He'll come back to get her.
长官 骚乱正在蔓延 希腊政府已经宣布紧急状态了
Sir, the rioting is spreading. The Greek government is declaring a State of Emergency.
B小组  继续寻找目标帕森斯
Bravo team, you'll be targeting Parsons.
发现目标
We got her.
四面包围  困住她
Split the team, put her in a box.
一位符合伯恩特征的嫌疑人刚抢夺了一辆警用摩托车
A suspect matcting Bourne's description has stole a police motorcycle.
他去寻找帕森斯了
He's coming for Parsons.
我们1号特工在哪  两分钟后抵达现场
- Where the hell is the asset? - 2 minutes out, sir.
帕森斯现在在雅典娜雕像附近 收到
- Parsons is at the statue of Athena. - Copy that.
B小组已阵亡
Bravo Team is down.
长官 1号特工已经抵达现场
Sir, the asset is arriving on scene.
把汽车上的摄像头投影到荧幕上  收到
- Pull up the dash cam. - Copy.
我要跟1号特工直接通话
Give me the feed in direct comm to the Asset.
已发现目标
Engaging targets.
我访问雅典警察战术数据。
I'm accessing Athens police tactical data.
我需要一颗监视卫星
I need eyes overhead.
调出所有可用的监视卫星源
Bring up the satellite's sweep.
长官 只有M和KH-12卫星可用
Sir, I'm showing a Misty and a KH-12 satellite available.
把KH-12调过来
明白 长官
- Connect to 12. - Yes, sir.
卫星监视已启动
Satellite video feed is online.
前方有警方设置的路障
Police have blocked the road to the north.
目标将会被迫左转
The target will be forced to turn left.
前方200米处又有一处路障 目标将会左转
Another barricade in 200 meters. Target turning left again.
伯恩准备转进小巷
Bourne's heading for the alley.
在山顶的左侧
Left at top of the hill.
这里有楼梯 他们往山东边去了
Stairway, up the hill Heading east.
给我一个可以狙击的点
Give me a strike point.
他找到一条出路
He's found a way out.
往左走200米 找到所罗门19号
200 meters to your left. 19 Solomou.
爬到屋顶
Get to the roof.
伯恩会从你视野内经过
Target should pass within your line-of-sight.
19 索罗门 收到
19 Solomon, copy.
调动卫星监视这几个坐标点
Focus the satellite on these coordinates.
当他到达那里给我锁定摩托车位置
And give me a lock on the motorcycle when it gets there.
收到
Copy that.
目标马上抵达和谐路
I've got the targets. They're approaching Emmanouil and Fidiou.
他们往西去了 德朗路
- Look west. - The long boulevard.
他们55秒后到你那边
Coming at you in 55 seconds.
收到
Copy that.
1号特工在线上
- The asset is online.
目标15秒后到你那边
Targets with you in 15 seconds.
5秒
5 seconds.
目标已经抵达你的视野范围内
Contact.
把头埋低
Stay low!
找机会开火
Find a shot.
抓紧了
Hold on!
恩在哪
Where's Bourne?
长官 直升机上的警察在1号特工
Ma'am, a police helicopter has spotted
所在的屋顶上发现了三具尸体
3 bodies on the roof near the asset.
警方马上抵达现场
A tactical team is on it's way.
妮琪
Nicky!
别动
Don't move!
警方战术小队已经进入建筑内
Athens police has entered the building.
特工 你得马上撤离
Asset, you need to get out of there.
这不可能
Negative.
我们甚至不知道伯恩的活着
We don't even know if Bourne's alive.
你想失去这个人吗
You want to lose this guy?
我是杜威局长 你还有20秒撤离时
This is Director Dewey, you have 20 seconds.
妮琪 坚持住
Hold on, Nicky.
我来救你了
I'm going to get you to cover.
不
No.
别过来..
No. Don't.
我马上过去..
I'm coming.
给我想办法定位达索的位置 明白 长官
- Get a location on Christian Dassault. - Yes, sir.
如果他确实和妮琪·帕森斯一起工作过
If he was working with Nikky Parsons, he will lead us to Jason Bourne.
找到她有助于我们找到杰森·伯恩
And let me know if you get a hit on that malware.
长官 我能问件事情吗
Sir, can I clarify one thing.
问吧
Yeah.
1号特工是不是认识伯恩
Does the asset know Bourne?
你怎么突然想起问这个
Why would you ask me that?
我看到了他在屋顶上的表现
His behavior on the roof-top.
似乎他们两个之间有所联系
It suggested a connection.
上次伯恩杀回来的时候 他曝光了黑蔷薇计划
The last time Bourne came back, he exposed the Black Briar program.
许多在外行动的特工被暴露了
It compromised active operations.
1号特工当时在叙利亚从事卧底工作
The asset was in Syria, undercover.
他被捕 饱受折磨
He was captured, tortured.
我们花了两年才把他救出来
And it took 2 damn years to get him out.
你觉得伯恩想搞到那些文件就是为了将它们公之于众
So you think that's why Bourne wants the files to go public again?
我可不知道他为什么突然杀了一个回马
I have no idea why he came back.
但是有一点很清楚 他所作的一切都是为了摧毁我们
But whatever he's doing, he wants to destroy us.
我们决不能让这种事情发生
We can't let that happen.
所以你无论收到什么消息 马上通知我
So you give me a call, as soon as you hear anything.
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
现在有请深梦集团创始人兼总裁 亚伦·卡罗尔讲话
And now the founder and chairman of Deep Dream, Aaron Kalloor.
嗨
Hi.
各位肯定知道自己为何到场  我们将会展示一个全新的平台
You all know why you're here. We're going to be unveiling a new platform.
我们认为这是大胆的一步 让我们能更好的为社会做出贡献
We think it is a bold new step, to allow us to serve our community better.
们的社交平台已经跨越了国与国之间的界限
We're a community right now that's trascending national boundaries, and
我们的用户量达到了15亿
I think we're at 1.5 billion users.
各位都知道 如今在社交平台圈内
In a nutshell. As you know we have an ecosystem of
共计有成百上千功能类似的社交应用
hundreds of thousands of apps at this point.
深梦集团旗下社交软件的这一全新平台将会整合
And what this new platform will do will be to integrate
用户的数据和个人偏
user's data and preferences,
我们将利用这些信息 去为每一位用户
and use that information, to enrich and tailor-make
量身定制 从而满足每一位用户独特的需求 这样的方式
each unique user experience, in a way that is frankly, unprecedented.
现在我能看到有一些记者举起了手上的笔 应该是要提关于个人隐私的问题吧
Now, I can see some journalists' pens twitching and ready to ask about privacy.
是的 是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
很多人都关心这个问题 这是毋庸置疑的
Uh. This is a concern of many people, and so it should be.
我们也很关心这一点 我想说的是
This is something that matters to us, and let me just say
我很能理解大家的想法 没人喜欢自己被监视的感觉
I understand nobody wants to feel like they're being watched
可以在这里郑重承诺 使用深梦集团旗下的社交应用及服务
So let just tell you, when you come to Deep Dream, when you use our service.
没有人会背监视
No one will be watching you.
卡罗尔 先生 这边请
Mr. Kalloor. Right this way, sir.
请慢用
Enjoy your meal?
谢谢你
Thank you.
恭喜啊
Congratulations.
听说你的股东们对你的新平台十分满意
I hear you stock-holders were very happy with the new platform.
我却听说 你们服务器被黑了
And I heard you got hacked.
我们能摆平的
We're dealing with it.
这件事彻底改变了我的想法 这么做风险太大
This changes everything. There's too much risk.
我不干了
I'm out.
艾伦
Aaron.
你是个才华横溢 很有洞察力的年轻人
You are an extraordinary gifted and perceptive young man.
先你同意与我们合作 因为你明白我们的国家正面临着重重威胁
When you agreed to help us it was because you understood the very grave threats...
你知不知道如果我们之前的安排公之于众
Do you have any idea the shit-storm I'll have on my hands
将会掀起一波多大的舆论风暴
if this arrangement becomes public?
史诺登那次泄密差点把我也拉下 而你却执迷不悟
I've already took a hit with Snowden, and you want more?
我们的敌人已经变的越来越狡猾了
Our enemies have become much more sophisticated.
仅仅大量收集外部数据是不够的
Gathering meta-data is no longer adequate.
我们需要在你的新平台上开一道后门
We need a backdoor into your new platform,
从而绕过信息加密
and a way past the encryptions.
以后这也无法满足你 也永远都不会满足
And when that's not enough, you'll want something new.
你是不是还不明白我的想法
You don't get it, do you?
隐私权 就像自由一样重要
Privacy is... is freedom.
我还以为你们会扞卫公民的隐私权
Oh I mean, that's something you should think about defending.
你这混蛋 当初我们赞助你成为一个亿万富翁的时候
You little prick, you didn't believe in privacy or freedom
怎么没听你嘴里叨叨这些所谓的隐私和自由
when we funded your start up that turned you into a billionaire.
我已经成百上千倍的回报给你们了
I have paid you back many, many, many times over.
我现在以及以后都会为之前做过的事深感不安
And I was never comfortable with any of this.
我不干了
I'm out.
我不会继续出卖我的客户了
I'm done selling out our customers.
你这么做就是出卖你的国家
Yet you would sell out your country.
事实上
The truth is,
你觉得你有危险
we wouldn't be having this conversation if you didn't feel
才会来找我谈话
personally at risk.
你以为在扞卫这些所谓的互联网自由
You talk about a free internet,
自己在拯救世界
you tell yourself you're saving the world,
但实际上你只是把世界变得更加危险
But all you're doing is making it a much more dangerous place.
而且你这样做更难扞卫自己的国家
And you sure as hell making this country much more difficult to defend.
你将会为此付出代价的 亚伦
And you're sure as hell accountable for that, Aaron.
应该负责
Accountable.
伯恩
Bourne?
把口袋里的东西全部掏出来 放在桌子上
Everything on the table.
把随身碟打开
Open it.
当然
Sure.
伯恩现身了
Bourne's surfaced.
在柏林
In Berlin.
马上派柏林分队行动
Get the Berlin team up.
她在哪
Where is she?
她死了
She is dead.
她知道这么做的风险
She knew the risks.
我已经警告过她了
I warned her.
她自己做出了选择
She made a choice.
你纯粹就是在利用她
You exploited her.
蓝队正在行动中
Berlin team is mobile.
那边发现了什么
What do we have on the location?
软件定位的地点与达索有所联系
It's an address linked to Christian Dassault.
有收到关于伯恩的消息吗 暂时没有
- Anything on Bourne? - Nothing yet.
正在接入当地监视系统
I'm accessing CCTV now.
长官 我有一个这样的想法
Sir, I've been thinking.
我们是不是搞错了
Maybe we got this wrong?
他有可能不是冲我们来的
What if he's not coming for us?
有可能是其它人在搞什么
What if it's something else?
你根本不知道你在对付的这位是怎样的一个人
You don't have any idea who you're dealing with.
我们应该多合作
We should work together more.
你曾经曝光过黑蔷薇计划
You exposed the Blackbriar program.
们的目标不是完全一致吗
We both are after the same thing, right?
我们都想摧毁那个控制着社会的腐朽机构
We both want to take down the corrupt institutions that control society.
我跟你不是一路人
I'm not on your side.
已经接入监控系统
CCTV feed is online.
他在电脑上浏览文件
He's on a computer.
我们得阻止他
We have to stop this.
如果他把那些文件公之于众
If he puts those files online,
我们的计划将会泄露 很多特工将会失去性命
operations will be compromised, and people will die.
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
至少你可以把这些文件都留给我
At least when you're done leave me the files.
这些肮脏的计划必须被公之于众
These programs have to be exposed.
人们有权了解它们
People have a right to know.
搞到那台电脑的控制权
We need that computer.
房间里有一台手机
There's a phone in the room.
我能利用它删掉电脑内的文件
I can use it to delete the files.
给他打电话 蓝队怎么还没到
- Got the phone. - Where's that team?
长官 还有五分钟抵达现场
5 minutes out, sir.
我们快没时间抓住他了
We're almost out of time, get to him.
听我说 大卫
Listen to me, David...
我做了一些事
I've done something.
做这些事
Something...
需要付出代价
That came at a cost.
总有一天 你会明白为什么的
One day you'll understand why.
我准备动身回到华盛顿去
I got to get back to Washington.
我爱你 儿子
I love you, son.
长官 房间里的两人打起来了
They're fighting, sir.
又搞定一层防火墙了
One more firewall.
长官 文件已删除
Files deleted, sir.
打电话给他
Call in.
伯恩 我叫希瑟·李
Bourne, my name is Heather Lee.
我不是这里的总负责人
I'm not in charge here.
你出走的时候我甚至还没来这里工作
I wasn't here when you went missing.
我能看到你在电脑上浏览以前绊脚石计划的文件
I can see you're going through the old Treadstone files.
你是在找寻你的过去吗
Were you tracing you history?
我知道你肯定是想找点什
I know you're looking for something.
让我来帮你吧
Let me help you find it.
把那电话给我
Give me that phone.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
杰森 我是罗柏·杜威 你还记得我吗
Jason, this is Robert Dewey. Do you remember me?
杰森 你的父亲是一位爱国者
Jason, your Dad was a patriot.
他清楚的看到我们伟大的国家
He could see the threats that America was facing, and like you
他出于崇高的使命感 选择为我们的国家服务
he chose to serve his country out of a profound sense of duty.
他肯定不希望看到今天的你 一步步的损害中情局的利益
He would not want to see you harm the Agency.
你必须收手
And you have to stop this.
你必须得马上收手
And you have to stop it now.
长官 我们预计到达时间
Sir, we're ETA...
守住这里
Take point.
上去
On it!
电梯
The elevator.
他跑了 长官
We lost him, sir.
马尔科姆 史密斯 承包商 总部位于伦敦
Malcom Smith, contract-only, based out of London
在上世纪90年代我们刚把伯恩招募进来 他负责所有“绊脚石计划”项目
Ran all of Tradestone's surveillance in the late 90s, when Bourne was recruited.
他还活着吗
Is he still active?
他现在主营私人安保业务
He's private security now.
通知1号特工 我要他6小时内抵达伦敦并准备好随时行动
Contact the asset and tell him I want him on the ground in London in 6 hours.
长官 我认为这可能只是场误会
I think that could be a mistake, sir.
误会怎么说
A mitake, why?
以前一直有一个说法 主张抓捕伯恩 而不是直接杀了他
There's an argument for catching Bourne, instead of killing him.
有意思 继续说
Alright, let's hear it.
伯恩已经消失很长一段时间了
Bourne's been off the grid for a long time.
他经历过很多黑幕 肯定看到了一些事情
He's been hiding in the shadows. He's seen things.
他肯定知道一些对我们有用的情报
He knows things that could help us.
把他重新招募进来 才是明智的选择
Bringing him back in, is the smart move.
你打算怎么做
And how are we going to do that?
阿尔伯特·赫希曼医生在伯恩结束项目的时候给他做了一份心理诊断
Albert Herchtz wrote a psych evaluation when Bourne left the program.
他的结论 伯恩内心里仍然是一个爱国者
He concluded Bourne is still a patriot at heart.
离开那个项目让他的内心永远无法平和
And that leaving the program could come back to haunt him.
你的意思是
And what are you suggesting?
我看到伯恩浏览的那些文件
I watched Bourne with those files.
他正拚命追寻他的过去
Desperately looking into his past and...
我认为他的心理平衡已经到了临界点了
I think he's at a tipping point.
如果我能跟他面对面谈
If I could get face to face with him.
我觉得我能把他重新招募回来
I think I can bring him back in.
就试这么一次
One attempt.
如果我失败了
And if it fails,
你们再杀他也不迟
you do what you have to.
恩 我觉得这个想法可行 鲍勃 你怎么看
Well, it makes sense to me. What do you think, Bob?
我们就试一次吧
Let's give it a shot.
好吧 开始安排吧
Alright, do it.
要么把伯恩招回来
Bring Bourne in.
要么就杀了
Or tie it off.
赶紧把这事了结了 谢谢 长官
- This ends now. - Thank you, sir.
长官 我很抱歉
Sir, I'm sorry.
不不不 没事
Oh, no. Don't worry about that.
孩子 你辛苦啦 去睡一会吧
Better get some sleep, kid.
你都一整天没阖眼了
You got a long 24 hours ahead of you.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
调试过程太慢了 怎么会突然发现这么多漏洞
It's taking too long, it shouldn't still be buggy this close to launch.
我认为那不是漏洞 我觉得稍微调整一下参数...
Well, I don't think it's buggy. I think we've changed some things
我觉得稍微调整一下参数...就能搞定了
that's gonna change the parameters, we're going to have to go and...
不行 万一搞不定我们还得费神把它们调整回来
Okay, then we need to change them back.
阿曼达 能麻烦你把备忘录交给凯尔吗  好的
- Amanda, can we get that note over to Kyle? - Absolutely.
听我说 我觉得你这么做没问题
Look, I don't... I... I think you're right.
但是我觉得我们不应该因此推迟发布会...
- I just don't think we want the... - I'm tired of this.
卡罗尔长官
Mr. Kalloor.
这是什么情况
What the hell is this?
卡罗尔长官 我是约翰 布朗
Mr. Kalloor, my name is John Barros.
我来自司法部
I'm from the Department of Justice.
我是来把这份起诉书交给你的
And I'm hereby serving you with the enclosed complaint
来自美国政府签发的 真的 在公共场合你必须这样做吗?
- issued by the US government. - Really, you have to do this in public?
起诉深梦集团违反谢尔曼法
against Deep Dream Corporation for violation of the Sherman Act.
次起诉要求你保存所有高管的私人以及公司的财产记录
This complaint requires you to preserve all personal and corporate financial records.
我们还将向联邦法院起诉深梦集团违反反托拉斯法
Pending anti-trust motions to be filed in Federal Court.
祝你好运 长官
Good day.
这肯定是杜威搞的鬼  亚伦
- This is Dewey. - Aaron.
这是一个信号
It's a message.
也许我们应该在事态恶化之前考虑好应该怎么做
And maybe we should think about what we're doing before it gets any worse.
你是不是觉得我们给他他想要的一切 他就会收手
So, you think if we give him what he wants, it will end there.
我只是说我们确实应该考虑一下同意他的要求
I'm just saying that maybe we should listen.
我要你整理出所有我与杜威的会面记录
I want you to pull up all the records of all the meetings I've had with Dewey.
所有的
All the records?
包括那些上不了台面的秘密谈话吗
Even the off thebooks discussions?
尤其是要把那些秘密谈话整理进来
Especially, those...
我要去拉斯维加斯了 准备开一份保险单
I'm going to Vegas, I need an insurance policy.
什么事
Yeah.
你到伦敦了么
You in London?
到了
Yes.
你为什么派她过来
Why are you sending her?
她有她自己的任务
She serves a purpose.
我一向独来独往
I work alone.
这次例外
Not this time.
不要把任务变成你的私人恩怨
Don't make this personal.
伯恩背叛了我们
Bourne betrayed us.
对我来说这就是私人恩怨
It's always been personal.
你知道你对手的能耐
You know who you're dealing with.
你最好做好准备随时行动
You better make sure you're ready.
什么事
Yeah?
深梦集团那边有新动作了
There's something you should know about Deep Dream.
但我需要一个保证
But I need an assurance...
我需要你的支持
that I have your support.
没有问题 你手上有什么消息
You got it. What do you have?
卡罗尔
Kalloor,
准备在拉斯维加斯的会议上搞出点名
is planning something, for Vegas.
哪位
Yes?
我是杰森·伯恩
This is Jason Bourne.
我要跟你谈谈
I need to talk.
谈什么
What about?
我早就不在中情局工作了
I don't work for the Agency anymore.
帕丁顿广场 15分钟后见
Paddington Plaza, 15 minutes.
伯恩刚刚打电话给史密斯
Bourne just called Smith.
他们15分钟后将会在帕丁顿广场见面
They're meeting at Paddington Plaza, 15 minutes.
一路上我们会盯紧史密斯的
We'll tail Smith the whole way.
看到伯恩以后 我去跟他见面
As soon as we get eyes on Bourne, I'll approach him.
保持低调 别闹太大乱子
Whatever you do stay contain.
我可不想事后被英国佬找麻
I don't want the Brits falling all over this asking questions.
明白
Understood.
这是追踪设备
Tracking device.
你在桥的南边等我
You'll hold on the south side of the bridge.
需要你时我会联系你
I'll contact you if I need you.
好的
Sure,
你是老板 听你的
You're the boss, right?
目标正在移动中 他朝运河方向去了
Subject is on the move. Heading towards the Canal.
A小组开始平行跟踪
Alpha Team take a parallel track.
B小组远距离跟踪
Bravo Team, follow the subject from behind.
同时注意查找伯恩的位置
And keep your eyes open for Bourne.
B小组 开始跟踪
Bravo Team, tailing subject.
我们出发
Let's go.
200米后右转
In 200 meters, make a right.
收到
Copy that.
检查通信设备 二号频道 听到请回答
Comms check, second channel. Do you copy?
收到 你现在在哪
I have you. Where are you now?
在跟踪史密斯
Heading towards Smith.
暂时没有发现伯
No sign of Bourne.
目标朝东边去了  进了一个小巷
Subject is turning east. Into an alley.
A小组注意 小巷通往一座天桥 走天桥就能追上他
Alpha Team, that alley leads to a foot bridge, which will bring him to you.
收到
Copy that.
已消灭B小组
Bravo Team is down.
我马上把最新路线发给你
Sending you updated route now.
收到了吗 史密斯
You copy that, Smith?
收到
Yes.
B小组 你们怎么停下了 什么情况
Bravo Team, why aren't you moving? What's going on?
B小组收到了吗
Bravo Team, do you copy?
什么情况 B小组现在在哪
What's happening, Heather, where's Bravo?
B小组通讯中断
We're comms down on Bravo.
A小组你现在能看到目标吗
Alpha Team do you have eyes on the subject?
我们紧着随后
We have eyes on him.
A队 请汇报情况
Alpha Team, sitrep.
A小组马上汇报情况
Alpha Team report.
希瑟 现在是什么情况
What's happening Heather?
A小组无人回复
Alpha Team isn't responding.
B小组呢
Bravo?
也无人回复
Still nothing.
两小组人都丢了希瑟
You lost both teams?
你控制不住局面 那可是神出鬼没的伯恩啊
Get a grip on this operation, Heather, that's Bourne.
下令出动1号特工吧
Bring out the asset.
长官 再给我点时间
Sir, I need more time.
我没时间给你了
We have no time.
你到底下不下命令
Are you going to give that order or not?
求您了 长官
Sir, please.
你真是太天真了 伯恩是不会回头的
If you're too naive to see the trees, there's no bringing in Bourne.
我们必须斩草除根
He has to be put down.
现在看来你显然已经无法果断的指挥了
And you obviously cannot do what has to be done.
下面由我来进行行动指挥
I am taking operational control.
1号特工 你可以开始行动了
Asset, you have a green light.
重复一遍 动手除掉伯恩
Repeat, you have a green light on Bourne.
收到
Copy that.
我已开始行动
I'm on my way.
1号特工 你在行动吗
Asset, are you on the move?
1号特工 为什么你的定位装置显示你是静止的
Asset, your tracking device says you're stationary.
你在移动中吗
Are you moving?
希瑟关闭通话器 让他专心工作
Heather, stay off this channel, let him do his job.
马上出发 去帕丁顿广场
Left tier. Get to Paddington Plaza fast.
收到
Copy that.
已就位
In position.
已锁定目标
Locked in.
什么情况
What's going on?
那边的噪音是怎么回事
What's that noise?
有几个火灾报警器响了
Multiple fire alarms.
肯定是伯恩搞的鬼
That's Bourne.
接下来我应该怎么办
What do I do?.
你站在原地别动
You stay there and you do not move.
请到最近的出口
Please proceed to the nearest available exit.
我不能呆在这
I can't stay here.
你保护不了我
You can't protect me.
史密斯 听我说 我要你呆在原地别动
I need you to stay where you are, Smith.
你还能看到他吗
You still have line of sight?
我正盯着他
I'm on him.
这边这么多人
You're going to shoot him?
他在我身边的时候你打得中他吗
In the crowd when he is right next to me?
史密斯 呆在原地别动
Stay where you are, Smith.
你知道他为什么要来找我
You know why he's here.
他就是想问个明白
He wants answers.
他来找他失去的东西了
You've lost this thing.
我必须得马上逃
I got to get out of here.
卧槽
Shit!
现在是什么情况
What the hell is going on?
伯恩带走史密斯了
Bourne's got Smith.
去追他们 我就在附近堵住他们的去路
Go after them. I'll come around and cut them off.
史密斯 我知道伯恩抓住你了
Smith, I know you're with Bourne.
你得想个办法让我们知道你在哪
You have to find a way to let us know where you are.
你为什么带我来这
Why are you taking me in here?
他们肯定就在广场附近
They got to be near the Plaza.
天啊 伯恩
Jesus, Bourne.
该死的
God damn it.
放松
Take it easy.
理查·韦伯
Richard Webb.
前贝鲁特情报站站长
- Station Chief, Beirut.
他是我的父亲 绊脚石计划的发起人
He was my father, he started Treadstone.
他付钱给你 让你监视我 为什么
- He hired you to put me under survellaince, why? - Jesus.
他为什么这么做
Why did he hire you?
史密斯 什么都别告诉他
Don't say anything, Smith.
不 不
No. No.
还是没发现他们
There's no sign of them.
我们现在怎么办
What do you want us to do?
继续沿着运河方向找
Work you way down the Canal.
我开车绕周围找 在那边跟你们碰头
I'll circle around and meet you there.
你跟着我去了贝鲁特
You followed my to Beirut.
那是我最后一次见到我的父亲
The last time I saw my father!
他明明能见到我 为什么还派你跟踪我
Why would he have you follow me?
这一切都说不通 为什么
It doesn't make any sense. Why?
一个字也别告诉他
Don't give him a god damn thing.
为什么
Why?
老天啊 伯恩 我会摔下去的
Jesus Christ, Bourne, I'm falling.
伯恩  饶了我吧
Bourne, please!
我能听见他们说话
I can hear them.
贝鲁特
Beirut!
我到那边是为了告诉他有人要我参与垫脚石计划
I went there to tell him that Treadstone had approached me.
但是他如果自己就是绊脚石计划中的一员 为什么他什么都不告诉我
But if it was his program, why didn't he say anything to me?
我做了一些事
I've done something.
做这些事
Something...
需要付出代价
that came at a cost.
他就是那天遇害的
That was the day he was killed.
他们说他是被恐怖分子杀死的
They said he was killed by terrorists.
杀手根本不是恐怖分子 对不对
He wasn't killed by terrorists, was he?
史密斯 想想你家人的生命安全 把嘴巴闭紧点
Think about your family's safety, Smith, and keep your mouth shut.
再不说话我就一枪崩了你
The next bullet is in your head!
为什么他们要派人杀我父亲
Why was he killed?
为什么
Why?
他是因为你才被杀的
He was killed because of you.
你的父亲 他没有参与到那个计划中
Your father, he wasn't in operations.
他之前不知道你被选中了 后来他发现了这件事
He didn't know we've chosen you. When he found out, he...
他威胁说要曝光整个项目
He threatened to expose the program.
他不想你变成一个杀人机
He didn't want you turned into a killer.
是谁杀了他
Who killed him?
别告诉他
Don't do it.
他在哪
Where is he?
他马上就到
He's almost there.
我们马上就能救你出来
We're going to stop this now.
求求你
Please.
上帝 快叫叫救护车
God! Someone call an ambulance!
有人需要帮忙 发生了什么
- Someone help. - What's happened?
他从五楼楼顶摔下去了
He went off the roof. 5 floors.
他应该是认出我来了
He recognized me.
我要去确保他已经死透了
I'm going to make sure it's finished.
警察已经在路上了
The cops are coming now.
大家散开 散开
Step aside, please. Step aside.
他逃走了  妈的
- He's gone. - Oh, shit.
我去追他
I'm going after him.
我沿运河方向继续找他
I'll work my way down the canal.
不了 你在伦敦的任务已经结束了
No. You're done in London.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
我这边还有一件事要你去办
There's another play to be made.
现在我们以前做过的那些事伯恩都知道
Now that he knows what we did, he'll come for both of us.
我们把握好机会 守株待兔即可
And that could be the opportunity for something else.
你的任务和复仇无
This isn't about revenge.
当然有关
Yes, it is.
不是他死 就是我亡
And it won't be done till one of us is dead.
现在去机场
Get to the airport.
腕计划这边有麻烦了
We have a problem with Iron Hand.
收到
Copy that.
汇报一下目前的情况
Give me a sitrep.
仍然一无所
We've got nothing.
继续找
Keep looking.
开车
Drive.
本来事情不会发展成这个样子的 我想跟你谈一谈
It wasn't supposed to go like this, I wanted to talk.
杜威要去哪
Where is Dewey going?
他要去拉斯维加斯 在网络峰会上跟亚伦·卡罗尔见
He's going to Vegas to speak with Aaron Kalloor at the cyber convention.
每年中情局都在那边招募新人
The Agency recruits there every year.
铁腕计划是什么
What's Iron Hand?
杜威发起的一项新的黑色计划
Dewey's new black ops program.
全频段监视
Full sprectrum surveillance.
也就是24小时监视所有人
Watching everyone all the time.
杜威需要卡罗尔跟他合作才能实施该项计
Dewey needs Kalloor's cooperation to bring it online.
让我下车
Let me out.
我可以想办法把你送进美国
I can help you get there.
你为什么帮我
Why would you do that?
跟你出发点不同 但是我们都想除掉杜威
You and I have different reasons, but we both want Dewey gone.
来 拿着这个
Here, take this.
我们维加斯见
I'll see you in Vegas.
长官
Sir.
我们会把卡罗尔之死嫁祸给一个虚构的伊拉克杀手
We're pinning Kalloor's hit on a fictional Jihadi shooter.
一位20岁的伊拉克公民
A 20 year old Iraqi national.
我们已经伪造了他的银行账户 出国证件 电子邮件以及通话记录
We created bank accounts, travel documents, emails, phone records.
暗杀看起来会像一次独狼行动 到时候会留下哪些物证
- He'll look like a lone wolf. - Any physical evidence?
1号特工完成任务以后会把枪留在原地 上面会有伊拉克人的指纹
The asset leaves the gun, it'll have the Iraqi's prints on it.
这个行动无需告知罗素(国家情报主管)
Russell doesn't need to know about this.
明白 长官
I understand sir.
有伯恩的消息么
Any news on Bourne.
暂时没有
Nothing.
他肯定会来追杀我的
He was always going to come for me.
就算他真的来了我们也能搞定他
Well, if it happens, we'll deal with it.
你上次去伦敦旅行的目的是什么
U.S. Air Security & Border Protection
你上次去伦敦旅行的目的是什么 迈克尔长官
What was the purpose of your visit to London, Mr. Michaels?
商务旅
Business.
欢迎回家 先生
Welcome home, sir.
谢谢
Thank you,
长官 我们在楼上给您准备了安全套房
Sir, we have a secure room for you, right upstairs.
祝您住宿愉快  谢谢
- Enjoy your stay. - Thank you.
您好 欢迎入住阿利亚宾馆
Hi, welcome to the Aria.
希瑟．李 我已经订过房了  好的 我查一下
- Heather Lee, checking in. - Okay.
我们给您安排了一个高层房间 房号2016
We have you in a lovely sky suite, number 2016.
祝您住宿愉快
Enjoy your stay.
谢谢
Thank you.
亚伦 亚伦
Aaron! - Aaron!
好了 亚伦
- Alright, Aaron!
找到李
Find Lee.
跟她说我上台前要见他一面
Tell her I want to see her before we go onstage.
好的 长官
Yes, sir.
我要后台和大厅里都布置好足够的人手
I want agents posted backstage as well as the auditorium.
好的 长官
Yes, sir.
亚伦
Aaron!
借过一下 让出一个道来
Coming through, make a hole.
嗨 伙计
Hi, guys.
怎么了 亚伦
Hi, how's it going? Aaron.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
谢谢 非常感谢
- Thank you. - Really appreciated.
什么事
Yeah.
你准备好了吗
You all set?
正在安排撤退路线
Checking the departure route now.
到时候你可得动作快点
You won't have much time.
放心 没人能发现我
They won't know where it came from.
我时间充足的很
I'll have enough time.
你解决了卡罗尔以后 我人会站在他在左边
After you take care of Kalloor, I'll be standing left hand at my side.
你给我也来一枪
You put a bullet in it.
好让大家以为我也是被暗杀的对象
It's better if I'm a target too.
收到
Copy that.
李
Lee.
长上台前要跟你谈谈
The Director wants a word before you go onstage.
我马上就去
Of course.
希瑟
Heather.
我的得意门生 我最坚定的支持者
My protege, and strongest supporter,
伦敦的事情之后 我一直想跟你谈谈
You know, after what happened in London,
但不知道怎么开口 我觉得
I did not know what to do with you.
那边的事情就当是
I suppose we'll just uh...
给你增加工作经验吧
Write it off to your learning curve.
很感激您的宽宏大量
I'd appreciate that.
至少上次的事情能让你明白 不要对伯恩抱有任何幻想
At least you can now see that you never had a chance.
下次伯恩出现的时候
When Bourne turns up again,
我来搞定他就行
I'll deal with him.
你明白了吗
Do you understand?
明白了
Of course.
我完全赞同您的意见
I agree completely.
到了台上之后 我来回答政策性问题
When we get onstage, I'll handle all the policy questions.
技术性问题就交给你了
Throw everything technical to you.
我会准备好的 长官  好 我们开始吧
- I'll be ready, sir. - Okay, let's do this.
亚伦 你好
Aaron.
罗柏 你好
Robert.
这位是希瑟·李
You know Heather Lee.
我们认识 她是我斯坦福大学的同学
Yeah, we went to Stanford together.
你在中情局工作的怎么样
Well. How are you enjoying life at the Agency?
我的工作富有挑战性 但是很充实
Challenging, but fulfilling.
是不是在那里挺难保持自己的个人原则
It's tough to stick to all your principles over there?
我一直恪守我的原则 谢谢您的关心
My principles are just fine, thanks.
长官们女士们 我们准备上场了 请跟我
Gentlemen, we're ready for you. Follow me, please.
这次会议一定会大获成功
I'm going to enjoy this.
我也这么觉得
So am I.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
大家好 今晚各位过的如何
Oh. Hi! How's everyone doing tonight?
参加这次会议
Welcome.
欢迎
欢迎来到今晚的网络峰会
Welcome to tonight's EXOCON symposium.
今晚我们很荣幸的请到了四位重量级嘉宾
We are so lucky to have 4 fantastic guests this evening.
中情局局长 罗柏杜威
The CIA Director, Robert Dewey is here.
我亲爱的朋友 同时也参加了前几届网络峰会的
And a dear friend of mine, and an old friend of EXOCON,
社交网络巨头深梦集团总裁 亚伦·卡罗尔
the CEO of social media giant, Deep Dream, Aaron Kalloor is here.
今晚的主题
Tonight.
是“加强网络监管”
Policing a free internet.
网络自由与公共安全哪个更为重要
Personal rights vs Public safety.
一直是我们这个时代的一个核心问题
This is the great question of our time.
我们今天做出的选择将会影响到我们的未
And the choices we make about this will determine our future.
下面我们直奔主题
So let's just dive right in, okay?
有请四位嘉宾上台
Come on out here, guys!
长官 有一条重要信息需要阅读
Sir, you got an incoming message.
高优先
High priority.
抱歉各位 我这里有点事需要处理一下
Alright guys, I'm going to have to take this.
我待会就上台
I'll catch up with you later.
去吧 没事
Go ahead.
谢谢 早上好
- Thank you. - Good morning.
看起来杜威局长暂时有点事不能上台
It appears Director Dewey is held up momentarily,
他告诉我说他马上就来
and I'm being told that it shouldn't be too much longer.
但我们今晚需要讨论的问题太多了 所以我们就先不等他了
But we have a ton of stuff to get into tonight, so we can start anyway.
克雷格 能让我说几句吗
Uh Brad, can I say a few words?
你说什么  能让我说几句吗
- Excuse me? - Can I get the ball rolling?
兄弟 当然可以
Oh sure, man. By all means.
女士们 先生们  欢迎亚伦·卡罗尔讲话
Ladies and gentlemen, Aaron Kalloor.
亚伦
Aaron!
谢谢 谢谢各位
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
谢谢各位
Thanks a lot.
杜威局长上台之前 我有些事
Before the Director comes out to join us,
想跟各位谈谈
I just wanted to share a few words with you guys.
很久以来 我一直就有这样的想法
A long time ago, I had this idea.
收到
Copy that.
面部识别系统发现伯恩了
Facial recognition got a hit.
他从伦敦希斯罗机场搭乘航班
Bourne was on a B.A. flight from Heathrow to Vegas.
于两小时前抵达拉斯维加斯
It landed 2 hours ago.
他怎么通过移民局审查的
How the hell did he get through immigration?
有人利用中情局权限让他的护照通过了安全审查
Someone issued him an Agency security clearance on his passport.
这是一个非常流行的想法。
Well it turned out to be a pretty popular idea.
全世界的人们都开始使用我们的应用
People from around the world started using our service.
好 首先
Well, first off.
这给我带来了很多意外的财富
This has all made me a lot more rich than it's probably...
我上台以后 把卡罗尔和那个女的都杀了
When I come onstage, take care of Kalloor and the girl.
收到
Copy.
我的意思是 大家都知道
What I mean to say is, you know.
所有的成功都需要付出代价
All this success has come at a cost.
在深梦集团内部有一颗毒瘤
There is a cancer at the heart of Deep Dream.
有一些不可告人的秘密
A guilty secret and uh...
现在 我想将它们公之于众
and I have to share it with all of you guys.
这狗娘养的想先下手把我们扳倒
The son of a bitch is about to take us down.
现在就动手 把那两个人都干掉
Take out Kalloor and the girl right now.
站住 好的
- Stay there. - Okay.
为了筹建我的公司
When I was starting out, I...
拿到了资金 跟他做了一笔交易
I took money to... start my company.
我从一个穿着黑西装的男人那里
I made a bargain with a guy in the dark suit.
现在 他要来找我的麻烦了
And now he's come back to take my soul.
我看到了狙击手
I see the shooter!
派人去抓杰森·伯恩
We got eyes on Jason Bourne!
他还有呼吸 快叫救护车
He's still breathing, call an ambulance!
快去啊
Let's go!
长官 我们得走了
Sir, we got to go.
我是瓦斯克斯 我在12楼发现伯恩
This is Vasquez. We're on Bourne.
准备好车 快
Get the cars ready! - Go!
马上把车准备好
Get the cars ready, right now!
不 把我送回套房
No. Take me to the suite.
长官 我们得把您送出去 伯恩就要来了
Sir, we got to get you out of here. Bourne is on the loose.
听我命令
You heard me.
送我回套房
Take me to the suite.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
保护他回套房 送他上楼
Take him to the suite! Take him upstairs!
就是现在 护送他到楼
Get him upstairs. Right now! Right now!
送他上楼
Up to the suite!
我们走 快 快 快
Let's go, right now. Go, go, go, go.
联邦警察 给我让开
Out of the way, federal agent!
瓦斯克斯 请汇报情况
Vasquez, sitrep.
瓦斯克斯 请回答
Vasquez, come in.
嘿 别动
Hey!
长官 我们发现他了
Okay, we've got him. Sir, this is Collier.
我们已经确认狙击手的身份了
We've IDed the sniper.
妈
Shit!
我们正在扩散他的照片
We're circulating his photo now.
发现伯恩了吗
What about Bourne?
正在找
Hang on.
发现他了 伯恩刚刚从西边后勤走廊 朝大厅方向去了
Okay, Bourne is just leaving the west service corridor heading for the lobby.
明白 盯紧伯恩
Copy that. Stay on Bourne.
现在什么情况
What?
我们还在找伯恩
We're still looking for Bourne.
并且他们已经确认1号特工的身份了
And they've IDed the asset.
回一楼 等待进一步指示
Go back to the first floor and wait for further instructions.
是 长官 收到
- Yes, sir. - Copy that.
所有人都趴下 站住
Everybody down! Right now!
趴下 让开  让开 让开
Get down! Move, move, move!
让开 全都让开
Out of the way! Federal agent, move!
带一队人坐东北角的电梯上去 我跟你在楼上会合
Take a team to the northeast elevator. I'll meet you up there.
伯恩去楼上找你了
Bourne's on his way up to you.
杰森 你怎么花了这么久才过
You took a long time to get here, Jason.
我已经查清贝鲁特的事了
I know about Beirut.
我也已经知道你的所作所为了
I know what you did.
今晚我们把这些恩怨都了结吧
It all ends tonight.
来 我们现在就来好好谈谈
Be a lot easier to do it right away.
你不是来复仇的
You didn't come here for revenge.
你回来是因为你知道你是时候回归了
You came here because you know it's time to come in.
你的父亲发起了这个项目
Your father created the program.
但却没能让它步入正轨
Didn't have what it takes to make it work.
但是你做到了
And you did.
你的能力一直都非常出色
You always did.
这也是你自己自愿加入这个项目的原因
That's why you volunteered.
我自愿加入这个项目 是我误以为那些恐怖分子杀了我的父亲
I volunteered because I thought our enemies killed him.
我自愿加入纯粹是因为一个谎言
I volunteered because of a lie.
不 你自愿加入是因为你了解你自己
No. You volunteered because of who you are.
你加入是因为你是杰森·伯恩
You volunteered because you are Jason Bourne.
而不是 大卫·韦伯
And not, David Webb.
32次暗杀行动 杰森
32 kills, Jason.
每一次你都完成的干脆利落
Every one of them made a difference.
政府都因为你英勇的所作所为变得更加安全了
People all across this country are safer because of what you did.
我都在尝试
Try to find another way.
你觉得你内心的挣扎有用吗
And how's that working out for you?
你的内心永远无法平和
You're never going to find any peace.
除非你能认清你自己究竟是一个怎样的人
Not until you admit to yourself who you really are.
杰森 是时候回来了
It's time to come in, Jason.
是时候回到我们的行动中来了
It's time to come in.
不
I can't.
我绝不为你工作
Not for you.
你从来都没到过这
You were never here.
你可以不用再逃亡下去了
You don't have to go after him.
你现在可以结束你的逃亡生涯
This can stop now.
你可以选择留
You have a choice.
我们走吧 准备好你的身份证!
Let's go, have your IDs ready!
准备好你的身份证
Have your IDs ready.
我们走吧 准备好你的身份证
Let's go. Have your IDs ready.
快点 伙计 快走 快走
Come on, guys. Let's go. Let's go.
到在大厅去
Go stand at the lobby.
拉斯维加斯警方,女士们 先生们
Las Vegas police, ladies and gentlemen.
一辆特警车和无牌照黑色道奇在阿利亚宾馆前被抢走
... was spotted in unmarked black Dodge Charger stolen from in front of the Aria.
站住 不要让它通过
- Stop it! - Don't let it through!
我的天啦
Oh my god!
开火
Fire!
开始行动
Move out!
让开
Move!
911 请求空中支援
911, to air units involve, identify.
这里是直升机一号 全体单位注意 嫌犯车辆
This is Air One, be advised, suspect vehicles have crashed
在里维埃拉酒店的东南入口发生车祸
into the southeast entrance  of the Riviera.
我们发现一位持枪歹徒逃入里维埃拉酒店南边的排水口
We have an armed suspect heading into the storm drain, south of the Riviera.
你是个叛徒 你一直都是个叛徒
You're a traitor. You've always been a traitor.
骨子里就是个叛徒
It's in your blood.
卡罗尔 先生
Mr. Kalloor. - Kalloor.
亚伦 你准备在会议上告诉我们什么
Aaron, what were you going to  tell everyone in the convention?
亚伦 你在隐瞒什么 准备什么时候告诉我们
- What are you hiding, Aaron? - What were you going to tell everyone?
为什么有人试图暗杀你
Why did somebody try to  assassinate you?
艾伦  深梦集团的核心问题是什么
Aaron, what's the cancer at the heart of Deep Dream?
眼下不方便做出任何评论
It'll be inappropriate to pass  any comment at this stage.
我很乐意配合有关部门的调查 尽快找出杀手的身份
But, I look forward to working with the authorities to find out who is responsible.
我现在要回深梦集团了 还有很多工作需要做
And in getting back to Deep Dream,  where we can continue our important work.
谢谢各位
Thank you.
长官
Sir.
我想说很抱歉 长官
I wanted to say I'm sorry, sir.
对于维加斯发生的事
About Vegas.
杜威局长的做法 很不明智
Director Dewey's tactics were unwise.
我们还得编一个故事来解释他留下的烂摊子
We're still trying to come up with a narrative to explain what happened.
那狗娘养的把我们所有人
That son of a bitch put a spotlight on Iron Hand.
都推到了媒体的聚光灯下
On all of us.
卡罗尔的事情还没曝光
Kalloor hasn't gone public yet.
我跟亚伦很熟
I know Aaron.
我们还能利用他
There's still moves we can make with him.
继续说
Tell me.
杜威已经成为过
Dewey's problem was that he belonged to the past.
像卡罗尔这样的人将会塑造未来
People like Kalloor are shaping the future.
我跟他一样 属于年轻一代
These are my people.
我知道该怎么跟他打交道
I know how to deal with them.
所以你想表达什么
And what do you want?
你任命新的中情局局长时
When you appoint a new Agency Director
你应该选一个能代表你的利益的人
You're going to need someone working for your interests.
选一个
Someone...
由你 直接任命的人
enpowered... by you.
伯恩的事你打算怎么办
What about Bourne?
你还想着把他招回来吗
You still think  you can bring him in?
他信任我
I have his trust.
在经历了这么多事情之后
After what we went through.
我有信心劝他回来
I'll bring him in.
我很有信心
I'm certain of it.
如果他不听你的
And if you can't?
那么
Then...
我们就除掉
he'll have to be put down.
你的提议很有意思
That's an interesting proposal.
你可以把车停在这边了
You can pull over here.
当然 如果你觉得你不需要我为你效力了
Of course if you decide that  you don't need me, then...
那也没问题
That's not a problem.
有很多部门都需要我这样有才华的人
There are many other agencies that would want what I know.
我给你带了点东西
I brought you something.
这个是用中情局纪念墙上象征着你父亲的那颗星星铸成的一枚徽章
It's a cast from you father's star, on the Memorial Wall at Langley.
对以前你遭遇的我感到十分抱歉
I'm sorry for what  happened to you.
那些残忍对待你的人
How you were treated.
都已经不在了
But the people who did that are gone.
而且
And...
中情局也有了不小的变化
things are changing at the Agency.
你想表达什么
What is it you want?
我知道你一直是一个爱国者
I know you've always been a patriot.
这个国家发生的事情 也一直牵动着你的心
And what happens to this country, matters to you.
国家需要你这样的人
We need you to help protect us.
回来吧
Come back in.
我们可以一起为国效力
And we'll work together.
我再考虑考虑
Let me think about it.
我要怎么联系你
How will I find you?
你还想着把他招回来吗
You still think  you can bring him in?
他信任我
I have his trust.
在经历了这么多事情之后
After what we went through.
我有信心劝他回来
I'll bring him in.
我很有信心
I'm certain of it.
如果他不听你的呢
And if you can't?
那么
Then...
我们就除掉他
he'll have to be put down.